Mostafa Gholami

Backend & Frontend Developer

https://mst-ghi.github.io/

4 +98 936 589 5522

O Isfahan, Iran

ABOUT ME

I have +8 years of experience in backend development with PHP and Node.js, utilizing frameworks such as Laravel and NestJS, as well as frontend development with Vue, Nuxt, React, and Next.js. Since 2020, I have focused on building applications with NestJS, Next.js, further honing my expertise in both backend and frontend technologies. Additionally, I have a background in multitenant projects, microservices architecture, Kafka, socket programming, Turborepo, caching strategies, and queue management.

SKILLS

- Nodejs
- Nestjs Framework
- Typeorm & Prisma
- Custom JWT & ACL
- · Microservice, Kafka

- Reactjs
- Nextjs Framework
- Turborepo
- React Query
- Redux & Zustand

- Docker
- Swagger
- Redis
- Caching
- SocketIO

WORK EXPERIENCE

Avid Advice

Full-time

October 2021 - October 2024

Karizor

Part-time

September 2023 - March 2024

Alert

Part-time

January 2023 - September 2023

Telebourse

Full-time

December 2020 - February 2022

Behina Gostar Nano

Full-time

November 2019 - November 2020

Parmand

Full-time

May 2018 - September 2019

Pardad Pardazesh

Full-time

August 2017 - May 2018

Barname Sazan

Full-time

May 2016 - May 2017

- --- Multitenant web app with Next.js for workouts, advice, legal, etc.
- → Used Turborepo for managing 5 web applications & 12 shared libraries
- ightarrow Using the Mantine UI library and Tailwind CSS
- -- Online class sessions, enabling real-time communication
- --> Page builder and admin panel for managing all content, users, sellers
- --> Microservices Architecture with Kafka
- -- Developed eight microservice using NestJS & Lumen
- --> Real-time Notifications implementation
- → Device Activity Logger for tracking device activities
- --> Microservices Architecture with Kafka & Redis
- --> Developed five microservice using NestJS & Lumen
- --> Real-time Notifications implementation
- $\ensuremath{\rightarrow}$ Operator Activity Logger for tracking user actions
- -- Utilizing web scraping techniques to gather stock market information
- $\ensuremath{\rightarrow}$ Designing and developing various financial charts
- --> Backend development using Nestjs and Lumen apps
- --> Frontend development using Nuxt.js
- --> Working on a comprehensive business system project
- $\ensuremath{\rightarrow}$ Developing backend apps using Nest.js and Laravel
- → Utilizing Redis for inter-app communication
- ightarrow Built web interfaces using Nuxt.js and Nextjs for various web apps
- --> Development of shopping and entertainment projects
- ightarrow Backend development using Laravel and Nest.js
- --> Frontend development using Nuxt.js
- $\ensuremath{\longrightarrow}$ Integration of payment gateway for secure transactions
- $\ensuremath{\rightarrow}$ Development of the marketer management project
- --> Developing backend apps using Lumen and Nest.js
- --> Frontend development using Nuxt.js
- --> Implementation of a dashboard for marketers
- -> Developed Frontend for websites using Blade and Reactis
- → Educational Platform and Legal Website

LONG-TERM PROJECTS

Social Media Platform

Social media platform designed to help users achieve their business goals and enhance their visibility. The backend of the platform is built using a microservices architecture with Java, while the frontend is developed using Turborepo and Next.js. Key features of the platform include a store, social media system, chat, online sessions and classes, various management sections, support for different businesses, and a website builder.

https://avidbizz.com/ https://seller.avidbizz.com/ https://backoffice.avidbizz.com/ https://builder.avidbizz.com/ https://api.avidbizz.com/

• Digital Brand Boards

The Digital Advertising Boards project was built with NestJS and Lumen, featuring eight microservices. The system allowed an Android app to communicate with the backend, enabling to display programs on digital billboards. The admin panel provided tools for designing ads program for various billboard sizes and scheduling content for each model, ensuring dynamic, time-based display management.

https://karizor.com/

• Intelligent Fire Fighting System

Developed an online fire safety and emergency services project using IoT for fire monitoring and alerts. The backend was built with Nest.js and Lumen using a microservices architecture and Kafka as a message broker, while the frontend was developed with Vue.js. Api subdomain changes periodically.

https://alert.ir/ https://my.alert.ir/ https://sfds.alert.ir

• Intelligent Fire Fighting System

Developed an online fire safety and emergency services project using IoT for fire monitoring and alerts. The backend was built with Nest.js and Lumen using a microservices architecture and Kafka as a message broker, while the frontend was developed with Vue.js. Api subdomain changes periodically.

https://alert.ir/ https://my.alert.ir/ https://sfds.alert.ir

• Iran's Capital Market

Utilizing web scraping techniques to gather stock market information. Designing and developing various financial charts. Backend development using two Lumen apps and one Nest.js app. Frontend development using Nuxt.js

https://telebourse.ir/ https://telebourd.telebourse.ir/ https://api.telebourse.ir/

• Material and Goods Supply System

Specialized social network for businesses. Developed using Nest.js, Next.js and Nuxt.js. It includes admin panel, service provider panel, web app, and mobile app. Backend consists of three Node.js applications that communicate with each other via Redis.

https://biz.tamuk.ir/ https://panel.tamuk.ir/ https://auth.tamuk.ir/ https://api.tamuk.ir

Online Flower Shop

Online flower, plant, and gardening equipment store using Laravel and Nuxt.js. This project includes the backend, vendor panel, admin panel, web app, and mobile app.

https://argegol.com/

Due to certain reasons, sponsor of this project is temporarily using WordPress for product sales.

Online Coffee Shop

Online coffee and coffee equipment store using Laravel and Nuxt.js. This project includes backend, admin panel, and a web app.

https://cafimafi.com/ https://cafimafi.com/api

SHORT-TERM PROJECTS

• Sadeghi Customs

Management panel for Sadeghi Customs, an auto detailing center, using Nest.js and Angular. The management dashboard was designed and implemented to oversee the center's activities.

https://sadeghicustoms.ir/panel https://api.sadeghicustoms.ir/docs#/

https://sadeghicustoms.ir/

Gym and Athlete Management

Gym management project that includes sports and nutrition programs, athlete management, and social features. The backend was built with Nest.js, and the frontend was developed using Next.js. https://maryamfatemi.com/ https://dashboard.maryamfatemi.com/ https://maryamfatemi-api.liara.run/docs

OPEN SOURCES REPOSITORIES

- Nodejs Projects & Libs
 https://github.com/mst-ghi/nodejs-projects
 Nestjs, Swagger, Prisma, Typescript, ...
- Reactjs Projects & Libs
 https://github.com/mst-ghi/react-projects
 Reactjs, Nextjs, Typescript, Mantine, ...

SOCIALS

- Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/mst-ghi/
- Telegram

 https://t.me/@mostafa_ghi

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Engineering
 Islamic Azad University

LANGUAGE

Persian ★★★★

• English ★★★

VISIT MY GITHUB PAGE TO CHECK OUT MY REPOSITORIES.